COSTA ANTON

Video Game Programmer

- @ costa.anton@hotmail.com
 https://antoncosta.github.io/

INTRODUCTION

Hello.

I'm Costa, a video game programmer from Romania. I am an open-minded, hard-working, individual who consistently strives to attain new knowledge and new experiences. Curiosity has always pushed me forward to try new things and I, without fail, have the perseverance to finish what I start. I consider myself to be a fast learner, or, at the very least, persevering enough to learn as quickly as possible. Apart from the education at universities in Romania I have done one semester in Krakow in Poland and 1 year of study in the Netherlands, both part of an ERASMUS scholarship. I have quickly adapted to both countries and have learned a lot from these experiences.

EXPERIENCE

European Economic Area(EEA) Placement Grant University of Iceland

Reykjavík, Iceland

 A two-month mobility in Iceland to work at the university on a research project. I developed a Virtual Reality application in the Unity game engine to help people that suffer from Acrophobia (fear of heights).

Full time Programmer/Localisation Engineer Pragmatic Play

m Jan 2019 - Jun 2019

P Bucharest, Romania

A Unity game engine developer for slots games. My task was
to create Unity editor extensions, or to continue existing
extensions, to help streamline the game production. I was also
part of the localisations team and we were responsible for the
maintenance of the application in the case that problems
might appear in certain languages.

Intern

Property Shark

Mar 2018 - Sep 2018

♥ Cluj-Napoca, Cluj, Romania

 A six-month period of internship. One half of it working with Visual Basic to do User Acceptance Tests. The second half was with C# creating and modifying ASP.NET applications. Both of them related the "PropertyShark - Real Estate Search and Property Information " website

Summer Intern

FIDA Solutions

Jul 2017 - Aug 2017

Paia Mare, Maramures, Romania

• Summer internship, worked 6 weeks with JavaScript, HTML and CSS.

SKILLS

Unity
C#
Unreal
C, C++
Java
Angular2
Python
JavaScript
Spring
Blender
Maya

INTERESTS

Technical

- Video Game Programming and Design
- Shaders & Computer Graphics
- Animation
- Sound Design

Hobbies

- · Playing video games.
- Writing fantasy stories.
- Travelling.
- · Listening to audio books.

LANGUAGES

English Romanian French Polish



STRENGTHS

Hard-working Fast learner Curious

Imaginative Adaptable

Game Engines

Video Game Design & Development

Mobile Applications

EDUCATION

Master's Degree, Graphics, Multimedia and Virtual Reality

University Politehnica of Bucharest

2018 - 2020

9 Bucharest, Romania

The Master focused on Computer Graphics mostly, OpenGL, C++ and video game engines, video game design and development, as well as a bit of marketing advice. Along with game engine, there was also an emphasis on Virtual Reality, as most university projects related to virtual reality were done by the computer graphics department.

Master's Degree, Computer Graphics

University of Groningen

2019 - 2020

Q Groningen, Netherlands

Part of an ERASMUS+ study exchange. I have continued the master's that I have started in Bucharest on Computer Graphics, Multimedia and Virtual Reality.

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science Babes-Bolyai University

2015 - 2018

♥ Cluj-Napoca, Romania

Web development focused, emphasis on OOP, it's principles and mobile applications as well as website development for mobile environments.

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science AGH University of Science and Technology

2017 - 2017

♥ Kraków, Poland

Exchange student for one semester with ERASMUS+. I mainly did courses in the field of Computer Science which were equivalent with what I would have done back home, one exception being a Polish Language course which was for exchange students.

High School, Mathematics and Informatics National College "Gheorghe Sincai"

2011 - 2015

Paia Mare, Romania

REFERENCES

Prof. Dr. Ing. Alin Moldoveanu @ alin.moldoveanu@cs.pub.ro

Dr. Jiří Kosinka @ j.kosinka@rug.nl